sharewareplaza.com 2014-02-09

# Privacy policy - SharewarePlaza

**Home » Privacy Policy**

SharewarePlaza.com Privacy policy

  * SharewarePlaza.com takes your privacy seriously. Because we gather certain types of information about our users we want to help you understand the terms and conditions surrounding the collection and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses the types of information we gather, how we use it, and how to correct or change it. These privacy practices apply to the Website that you were viewing when you clicked through to this policy, which is operated by SharewarePlaza.com or its partner.
  *   
This site contains links to other sites. SharewarePlaza.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Websites.
  *  **Usage Tracking**

  * SharewarePlaza.com tracks user traffic patterns throughout SharewarePlaza.com and this information is correlated with data about individual users. Overall usage statistics, according to a user's domain name, browser type and MIME type gotten by reading this information from the browser string (information contained in every user's browser), are also broken down.
  *   
SharewarePlaza.com also tracks and catalogs the search terms that customers enter into our search tools, but this tracking is never associated with individual users.
  *  **Cookies, IP & Log files**

  * In order to offer you a personalized service, SharewarePlaza.com may use cookies to ease storing and tracking your preferences. For instance, we may use cookies to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly, or to deliver content specific to your interests; the content contained is not distributed to third parties.
  *   
Advertisements served by Google, as a third party vendor, use DART cookies. These cookies are used to serve ads based on your visit to this site and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the [DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).
  *   
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Website. We will not use this information in any other way and will not release the information to any third parties.
  *   
SharewarePlaza.com automatically logs the following information about visitors to this website: IP addresses, browser type, domain names, access times and the number of hits to specific pages within the site. This information is used to administer the site and to evaluate its usability. This information is not used to create any type of personal profiles for the visitors. 
  * **Copyright**

  * All editorial content and graphics on SharewarePlaza.com are protected and may not be copied without the permission of SharewarePlaza.com, which reserves all rights. If you see a violation of copyright about our site, please do not hesitate to let us know by mailing [webmaster@sharewareplaza.com](mailto:webmaster@sharewareplaza.com) and we will deal with the rest. The downloads which are listed on our page are copyrighted by their authors. If you see a violation of copyright about any products listed on our site, please email us to report it immediately and it will be removed.
  *  **Security**

  * This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Use of software author names, addresses and any other personal information is used only in our announcements and is not released to third parties nor do we send any mail to the return addresses offering or soliciting any services.
  *  **Contacting the Website**

  * If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Website, you can contact [webmaster@sharewareplaza.com](mailto:webmaster@sharewareplaza.com)
